{
    "classes": [
        "PERSON",
        "ORG",
        "LOC",
        "PRODUCT",
        "DATE",
        "DATA_AI",
        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH",
        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY",
        "FINANCE",
        "CONFERENCE"
    ],
    "annotations": [
        [
            "Terminologies that was created by knowledge of members. PER: Andrew Ng, Steve Jobs, Ralph Merkle, Stuart Haber, W.Scott Stornetta, Satoshi Nakamoto, user, consumer, producer, developer, investor,  leader, Caroline Pham, commissioner, Gary Gensler, CEO. ORG: Oracle, Google, Meta, Apple, Amazon, Viettel, UNICEF, WTO, Multicoin Capital, Commodity Futures Trading Commission. LOC: New York, London, Paris, Tokyo, Shanghai, Peking, HongKong, New South Wales, US, UK, France, Japan, China. PRODUCT: Apps, website, applications. DATE: June 21st, September 15th, 01/01/2023, May 16th 2004, December 12th 2024, 2017, 2024, Oct. 1 . DATA_AI: Machine learning, Data, Artificial intelligence, Deep learning, Bigdata, database, cluster, regression, autoregressive, patterns. BLOCKCHAIN: Blockchain, Crypto currencies, Bitcoin, BTC, Dogecoin, smart contracts, block, hash function, peer-to-peer,P2P consensus mechanism, Cryptography, Distributed ledger, Proof-of-work, Proof-of-stake, Encryption, Digital signature, EVM, Ethereum, decentralization, distributed network, Hyperledger fabric,  Corda, Quorum, BaaS, Blockchain as a Service, Crypto, FTX,  ETF. OTHER_IT_TERMILOGIES: Server, client, network, docker, code, TCP/IP, protocol, bandwidth, cache, Cloud, Cookie, CPU, GPU, CSS, CSP, Cyber-insurance, Cyber Physical Attacks, DDoS attacks, desktop, DevOps, DHCP, DNS, domain, edge computing,  Ethernet, Firewall, gateway, HTTP, IoE, IoT. FINANCE: transactions, contracts, assets, capital gain, balance sheet, capital market, cash flow, depreciation, equity, amortization, trademark, investment,  market, fund, $1.36, venture. CONFERENCE: Blockchain Africa Conference, Blockchain Expo, Europe, European Blockchain Convention, Blockchain Futurist Conference, International Congress on Blockchain and Applications, Blockchain Economy Istanbul, Paris Blockchain Week",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        61,
                        70,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        72,
                        82,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        84,
                        96,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        98,
                        110,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        112,
                        129,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        131,
                        147,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        149,
                        153,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        155,
                        163,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        165,
                        173,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        175,
                        184,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        186,
                        194,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        197,
                        203,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        205,
                        218,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        220,
                        232,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        234,
                        246,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        248,
                        252,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        258,
                        264,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        266,
                        272,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        274,
                        278,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        280,
                        285,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        287,
                        293,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        295,
                        302,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        304,
                        310,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        312,
                        315,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        317,
                        334,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        336,
                        373,
                        "ORG"
                    ],
                    [
                        379,
                        387,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        389,
                        395,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        397,
                        402,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        404,
                        409,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        411,
                        419,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        421,
                        427,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        429,
                        437,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        439,
                        454,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        456,
                        458,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        460,
                        462,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        464,
                        470,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        472,
                        477,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        479,
                        485,
                        "LOC"
                    ],
                    [
                        495,
                        499,
                        "PRODUCT"
                    ],
                    [
                        501,
                        508,
                        "PRODUCT"
                    ],
                    [
                        510,
                        523,
                        "PRODUCT"
                    ],
                    [
                        530,
                        539,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        541,
                        555,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        557,
                        567,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        569,
                        582,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        584,
                        602,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        604,
                        608,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        610,
                        614,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        616,
                        622,
                        "DATE"
                    ],
                    [
                        634,
                        650,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        652,
                        656,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        658,
                        681,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        683,
                        696,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        698,
                        705,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        707,
                        715,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        717,
                        724,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        726,
                        736,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        738,
                        752,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        754,
                        763,
                        "DATA_AI"
                    ],
                    [
                        776,
                        786,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        788,
                        805,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        807,
                        814,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        816,
                        819,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        821,
                        829,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        831,
                        846,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        848,
                        853,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        855,
                        868,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        870,
                        882,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        883,
                        886,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        887,
                        906,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        908,
                        920,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        922,
                        940,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        942,
                        955,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        957,
                        971,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        973,
                        983,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        985,
                        1002,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1004,
                        1007,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1009,
                        1017,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1019,
                        1035,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1037,
                        1056,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1058,
                        1076,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1079,
                        1084,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1086,
                        1092,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1094,
                        1098,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1100,
                        1123,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1125,
                        1131,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1133,
                        1136,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1139,
                        1143,
                        "BLOCKCHAIN_TECH"
                    ],
                    [
                        1166,
                        1172,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1174,
                        1180,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1182,
                        1189,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1191,
                        1197,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1199,
                        1203,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1205,
                        1211,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1213,
                        1221,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1223,
                        1232,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1234,
                        1239,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1241,
                        1246,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1248,
                        1254,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1256,
                        1259,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1261,
                        1264,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1266,
                        1269,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1271,
                        1274,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1276,
                        1291,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1293,
                        1315,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1317,
                        1329,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1331,
                        1338,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1340,
                        1346,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1348,
                        1352,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1354,
                        1357,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1359,
                        1365,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1367,
                        1381,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1384,
                        1392,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1394,
                        1402,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1404,
                        1411,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1413,
                        1417,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1419,
                        1422,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1424,
                        1428,
                        "OTHER_IT_TERMINOLY"
                    ],
                    [
                        1438,
                        1450,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1452,
                        1461,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1463,
                        1469,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1471,
                        1483,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1485,
                        1498,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1500,
                        1514,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1516,
                        1525,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1527,
                        1539,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1541,
                        1547,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1549,
                        1561,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1563,
                        1572,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1574,
                        1584,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1587,
                        1593,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1595,
                        1599,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1601,
                        1606,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1608,
                        1616,
                        "FINANCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1629,
                        1657,
                        "CONFERENCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1659,
                        1674,
                        "CONFERENCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1684,
                        1714,
                        "CONFERENCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1716,
                        1746,
                        "CONFERENCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1748,
                        1801,
                        "CONFERENCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1803,
                        1830,
                        "CONFERENCE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1832,
                        1853,
                        "CONFERENCE"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ]
    ]
}